{
    "id": "7e820d0748674303a18586f41e4b64db",
    "title": "Prepositions or No Prepositions",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "e3b7d5439a114ffab053f01dd2115046",
            "title": "Prepositions Or No Prepositions",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Let’s ……………………. your plans.",
                    "description": "Discuss is followed by a direct object without any preposition.",
                    "answers": [
                        "discuss",
                        "discuss about",
                        "discuss on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ……………………… a cousin of hers.",
                    "description": "Marry is followed by a direct object without any preposition.",
                    "answers": [
                        "married",
                        "married with",
                        "married to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The baby …………………….. her mother.",
                    "description": "Resemble is followed by a direct object without any preposition.",
                    "answers": [
                        "resembles",
                        "resembles to",
                        "resembles with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will never forget meeting her …………………….. afternoon.",
                    "description": "Prepositions are often omitted before time expressions beginning this or that.",
                    "answers": [
                        "on that",
                        "that",
                        "in that"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The conference is ………………………. Friday.",
                    "description": "Prepositions are often omitted before time expressions beginning this or that.",
                    "answers": [
                        "this",
                        "on this",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We met ……………………….. Friday in February.",
                    "description": "Prepositions are often omitted before time expressions beginning one.",
                    "answers": [
                        "one",
                        "on one",
                        "at one"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was up ……………………. night.",
                    "description": "Prepositions are often omitted before time expressions beginning all.",
                    "answers": [
                        "all",
                        "on all",
                        "in all night"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Susie has agreed to come …………………….. morning.",
                    "description": "Sometimes we leave out on before the names of the days of the week. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Monday",
                        "on Monday",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He calls his mother three times ……………………. day.",
                    "description": "No preposition is used in the expression …. times a day.",
                    "answers": [
                        "a",
                        "in a",
                        "on a"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Private lessons cost 20 dollars ………………….. hour.",
                    "description": "No preposition is used in this expression. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "for an",
                        "in an",
                        "an"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………………. day is your interview?",
                    "description": "In an informal style, we can leave out on before what day.",
                    "answers": [
                        "On what",
                        "What",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………….. time does the train arrive?",
                    "description": "What time sounds more natural than at what time. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "At what",
                        "On what"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}